Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Conservation, 1902-2001; Series II; 21.5 linear feet
  - Fair Chase and Other Positions, 1959-2001; Subseries 3; 1.0 linear foot
    - Gun Control, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 108/3)
    - Gun Control, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 108/4)
    - Hunting on Preserves, Reservations, and Enclosed Areas, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 108/5)
    - Illegal Trophy Hunting, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974 (Box-folder 108/6)
    - Marine Mammal Commission, Conservation, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 108/7)
    - Polar Bear, 1965 (Box-folder 240/3)
    - Position Papers, Mailing, 1996 (Box-folder 108/8)
    - Position Papers, Responses, 1996 (Box-folder 108/9-11)
    - Position Statements Committee, Report, 1999 (Box-folder 108/12)
    - Public Hunting in National Parks, 1963 (Box-folder 108/13)
    - Statement of Daniel A. Poole before the Subcommittee on National Parks and Recreation, Sawtooth National Forest, 1971 (Box-folder 108/14)
    - Wildlife Conservation Partners Committee, Strategic Plan for the Boone and Crockett Club, 2001 (Box-folder 227/5)
  - Conservation Awards, 1983-1995; Subseries 4; 0.375 linear feet
    This subseries contains correspondence, endorsements, and additional materials related to conservation awards given to Club members as well as conservation awards given by the Club.
    - Alexander Calder Conservation Award, Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 109/1)
    - Boone and Crockett Club and International Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, Ethics Award, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 109/2)
    - Bureau of Land Management Award, 1991 (Box-folder 109/3)
    - Certificate of Recognition for Support in Furthering Conservation, undated (Box-folder OS 223/x)
    - Chevron Conservation Awards, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 109/4)
    - Chevron Conservation Awards, Packet, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 109/5)
    - Chevron Conservation Awards, Packet, 1990 (Box-folder 109/6)
    - International Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, Boone and Crockett Club Award, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 109/7)
    - International Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, Boone and Crockett Club Award, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 109/8)
    - President's Environmental and Conservation Challenge Awards, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 109/9)
    - The Wildlife Society, Wildlife Student Award Program, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 109/10)
  - Campaigns, 1982-1996; Subseries 5; 1.25 linear feet
    This subseries contains correspondence, promotional packets, catalogs and mailers related to the Club’s conservation and fundraising campaigns. Included here are materials related to the Club’s conservation stamp print fundraising effort as well as the Blazing New Trails for Conservation campaign.
    - Blazing New Trails for Conservation, The Boone and Crockett Campaign for Wildlife, Fundraising and Development Reports, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 109/11)
    - Blazing New Trails for Conservation, The Boone and Crockett Campaign for Wildlife, Pamphlets, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 109/12)
    - Boone and Crockett Wildlife Conservation Program, Products, Volume I, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 215/0)
    - Boone and Crockett Wildlife Conservation Program, Products, Volume II, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 215/0)
    - Conservation Fund, Contributions, 1990 (Box-folder 109/13)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Artist Competition Information, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 109/14)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Artist Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 109/15)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 109/16)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Hunter's Quest Article, 1990 (Box-folder 109/17)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Inventory, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 109/18)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Inventory, undated (Box-folder 109/19)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Invoices and Receipts, 1988 (Box-folder 109/20)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Order Transmittal, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 109/21)
    - Conservation Stamp Prints, Revenues, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 109/22)
    - Hopkins Rifle Conservation Raffle, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 109/23)
    - Hopkins Rifle Conservation Raffle, Mailer, 1982 (Box-folder 109/24)
    - Hopkins Rifle Conservation Raffle, Mailer Materials, undated (Box-folder 109/25)
- Big Game Records, 1906-2002; Series III; 29.75 linear feet
  This series documents the Club’s big game records activities including the evolution of the management of the Big Game Records program as well as materials related to Official Measurers, the Sagamore Hill Medal Program, and the National Collection of Heads and Horns. This series has been divided into five subseries and includes committee meeting minutes, correspondence, Awards Program planning materials, menus, invitations and trophy certificates, as well as correspondence and inventories related to the National Collection of Heads and Horns.
  Materials in this series arrived at the archives with no discernable original order and were grouped and interfiled by the processor to reflect historic and current organization of the Club’s big game records keeping activities and management. Series are arranged alphabetically and original order within folders was maintained.
  Note: Trophy records and related photographs are maintained at the Boone and Crockett Club headquarters in their Big Game Records Department.
  - Administration, 1931-1999; Subseries 1; 17.25 linear feet
    This subseries has been divided into three subseries and documents the administration of the club’s big game records program. Established in 1935, the Records of North American Big Game Committee supervised the Big Game Competitions until the Club began collaborating on Big Game Records with the National Rifle Association in 1973. At that time, the administrative duties fell to the North American Big Game Awards Program, which was housed in the Hunting Activities Department of the National Rifle Association. Currently, Big Game Records are administered in collaboration with the North American Big Game Committee and professional staff.
    This subseries is divided into three sub-subseries which reflect the evolution of the management of Big Game Records at the Boone and Crockett Club.
    - Committees, 1931-1999; Sub-subseries 1; 11.25 linear feet
      This sub-subseries contains materials related to committee involvement in Big Game Records keeping.
      - Committee - Records of North American Big Game, 1931- 1999; Sub-sub-subseries 1; 10.5 linear feet
        Sub-sub-subseries 1 includes materials produced by the Records of North American big Game Committee. In the years from 1935 through 1973, the Committee managed and oversaw the Club’s big game records-keeping efforts including the North American Big Game Awards Programs. Of particular interest are correspondence to and from Grancel and Betty Fitz that documents changes in the trophy scoring system. Additionally, this sub-sub-subseries contains meeting minutes, correspondence, trophy score sheets and materials related to scoring from 1939 through 1993. Absent are correspondence or meeting minutes created by the Committee before 1944.
        - 1947 Brochure on Competitions, Correspondence, 1947-1968 (Box-folder 110/1)
        - Alaska Big Game Trophy Club, Alaskan Air Command, and Alaska Sportsman, Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 110/2)
        - Alaskan Bears, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 110/3-4)
        - Alaska Brown Bear/Grizzly Bear Reclassification, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 110/5)
        - Alaskan Bears and Mule Deer Scoring, Warren page, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 110/6)
        - Alaskan Bears, Dr. R.L. Rausch, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 110/7)
        - Alaskan Brown Bear Scoring, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 110/8)
        - Alaskan Bears, Scoring, 1963 (Box-folder 110/9)
        - Alaskan Bears, Scoring, James W. Brooks, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 110/10)
        - Alaskan Grizzly, Grancel Fitz, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 110/11)
        - Alaskan Grizzly Articles by Grancel Fitz, Drafts, 1962 (Box-folder 110/12)
        - Announcements and Mailers, 1950-1963 (Box-folder 110/13)
        - Arizona Wildlife Trophies, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 110/14)
        - Articles and Clippings, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 111/1)
        - Articles and Clippings, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 111/2)
        - Bear Classification, Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 111/3)
        - Big Game Brochure, Illustration Originals, 1947 (Box-folder 111/4)
        - Big Game Films, 1960 (Box-folder 111/5)
        - Big Game Photographs, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 111/6)
        - Big Game Photographic Competition, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 111/7)
        - Big Game Records Holders, 1971 (Box-folder 111/8)
        - Big Horn Sheep, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 111/9)
        - Bison, Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 111/10)
        - Black Bear Workshop, Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 111/11)
        - Blacktail Deer, Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 112/1)
        - Bow Hunting, 1948-1969 (Box-folder 112/2)
        - W. Douglas Burden, Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 240/4-6)
        - W. Douglas Burden, Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 112/3)
        - California Bighorn, 1991 (Box-folder 112/4)
        - Canadian Trophies, 1967 (Box-folder 112/5)
        - John Caputo, Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 112/6)
        - Caribou Entries from Quebec and Labrador, 1968 (Box-folder 112/7)
        - Chicago Natural History Museum, Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box-folder 112/8)
        - James L. Clark, Big Game Trophy Scoring Methods, 1945 (Box-folder 112/9)
        - Clove Valley Rod and Gun Club, Committee Minutes and Reports, 1985 (Box-folder 112/10)
        - Competition Procedures, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 112/11)
        - Competitions and Record Keeping, Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 240/7)
        - Computerization of Records, Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 112/12)
        - Copyright, 1950-1980 (Box-folder 112/13)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 112/14)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1947 (Box-folder 112/15-17)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948 (Box-folder 112/18-19)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1949 (Box-folder 113/1)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 113/2-4)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 113/5-7)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 114/1)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 114/2-6 (1-5 of 6))
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 115/1 (6 of 6))
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 115/2-7)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 116/1)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 116/2)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 116/3)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 116/4)
        - Cougar, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 116/5)
        - Dallas Morning News, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 116/6)
        - Daniel Boone Farm, Correspondence, 1944-1967 (Box-folder 116/7)
        - Deer, 1955-1970 (Box-folder 116/8)
        - Deer, Elk, and Moose Scoring Methods, 1961-1988 (Box-folder 116/9)
        - Double Penalty in Scoring, 1981 (Box-folder 116/10)
        - Dub Polar Bear Scoring, Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 117/1)
        - Endangered Species, Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 117/2)
        - Entry Fees for Competitions, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 117/3)
        - Entry Requirement Review, 1982 (Box-folder 117/4)
        - Expeditions, 1937-1951 (Box-folder 117/5)
        - Field and Stream, Correspondence, 1949-1975 (Box-folder 117/6)
        - Final Report to Club Treasurer, 1972 (Box-folder 117/7)
        - Finances, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 117/8)
        - Financial Report, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 117/9)
        - Betty Fitz, Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 117/10)
        - Betty Fitz, Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 117/11)
        - Grancel Fitz, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 117/12)
        - Grancel Fitz, Trophy Rating System, 1939-1948 (Box-folder 117/13)
        - Foreign Big Game Association, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 117/14)
        - Garcia Mule Deer, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 117/15)
        - General Inquiries, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 117/16)
        - Grizzly Bear, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 118/1)
        - History of Records Keeping, 1951-1974 (Box-folder 118/2)
        - Honseth Canada Moose, 1965 (Box-folder 118/3)
        - Hunting in Germany, Correspondence, 1931-1963 (Box-folder 118/4)
        - Income and Expenditures, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 118/5)
        - Income and Social Security Tax Materials, 1936-1941 (Box-folder 118/6)
        - Items for Discussion, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 118/7)
        - Items for Resolution, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 118/8)
        - Jaguar, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 118/9)
        - Jordan Whitetail Deer Dispute, 1963-1978 (Box-folder 118/10)
        - King of Nepal, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 118/11)
        - Kis Bighorn Sheep Dispute, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 118/12)
        - Madison Grant Reserve for Protection of Roosevelt Elk, and Conservation Committee Ledger, 1935-1949 (Box-folder 118/13)
        - Listings in Encyclopedia Britannica, 1978 (Box-folder 118/14)
        - Loans of Photographs and Materials, Correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 118/15)
        - Measurement Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 118/16)
        - Measuring Instruments for Judging, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1969 (Box-folder 118/17)
        - Measuring Techniques and Procedures, Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 118/18)
        - Medal Design, 1947-1983 (Box-folder 118/19)
        - Metalic Arts Co., Correspondence and Invoices, 1960-1983 (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1947-1951 (Box-folder 119/2)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 119/3)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 119/4-5)
        - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 119/6-7)
        - Meeting Agendas, 1966 (Box-folder 119/8)
        - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 119/9)
        - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 120/1)
        - Meeting Agendas, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 120/2)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 120/3)
        - Meeting Minutes, Addendum, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 240/8)
        - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 120/4)
        - Memoranda, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 120/5)
        - Meeting Agendas, Correspondence, and Meeting Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 120/6-7)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 120/8)
        - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 120/9)
        - Member Mailers, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 120/10)
        - Minimum Scores, Correspondence, 1933-1971 (Box-folder 120/11)
        - Minimum Score Changes, Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 120/12)
        - Montana Heads, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 121/1-2)
        - Moose, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 121/3)
        - Move to Carnegie Museum, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 121/4)
        - Muskox, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 121/5)
        - Muskox Scoring Methods, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121/6)
        - National Rifle Association, Correspondence, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 121/7-9)
        - National Rifle Association, Correspondence, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 121/10)
        - National Sportsman's Club, Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 122/1)
        - Non-Typical Wapiti, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 122/2)
        - Official Measuring Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 122/3)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, circa 1935-1961 (Box-folder 122/4-5)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1963 (Box-folder 122/6-7)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1965 (Box-folder 122/8-10 (1-3 of 5))
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1965 (Box-folder 123/1-2 (4-5 of 5))
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1981 (Box-folder 123/3)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1988 (Box-folder 123/4)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, 1999 (Box-folder 123/5-6)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, Approved Changes, 1981 (Box-folder 123/7)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, Copyrights, 1950-1993 (Box-folder 123/8)
        - Official Score Sheets for Big Game Trophies, Requests, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 123/9)
        - Official Scoring System, Correspondence and Drafts, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 123/10)
        - Jack S. Parker, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 123/11)
        - Jack S. Parker, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 123/12 (1 of 2))
        - Jack S. Parker, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 124/1 (2 of 2))
        - Pennsylvania Game Commission, Deer Records Program, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 124/2)
        - Dorothy G. Petrovsky, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 124/3)
        - Polar Bear, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 124/4-7)
        - Polar Bear, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 125/1-2)
        - Policy Statements, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 125/3)
        - Pope and Young Club, Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 125/4)
        - Pope and Young North American Big Game Trophy Competition, Score Chart Permission Request, 1950-1993 (Box-folder 125/5)
        - Press Releases, 1948-1971 (Box-folder 125/6)
        - Printing, Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 125/7)
        - Problem Trophy Cases, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 125/8-10)
        - Procedure in Handling Score Charts, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 125/11)
        - Pronghorn Antelope, 1936-1970 (Box-folder 125/12)
        - Pronghorn Antelope Scoring Methods, 1970-1986 (Box-folder 125/13)
        - Publicity, 1976 (Box-folder 125/14)
        - Range of Coues and Whitetail Deer, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 125/15)
        - Reports, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 241/1)
        - Report, 1967 (Box-folder 125/16)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, January, 1971 (Box-folder 126/1)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, February, 1971 (Box-folder 126/2)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, May, 1971 (Box-folder 126/3)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, June, 1971 (Box-folder 126/4)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, July, 1971 (Box-folder 126/5)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, September, 1971 (Box-folder 126/6)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, October, 1971 (Box-folder 126/7)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, November, 1971 (Box-folder 126/8)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, January, 1972 (Box-folder 126/9)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, February, 1972 (Box-folder 126/10)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, March, 1972 (Box-folder 126/11)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, April, 1972 (Box-folder 126/12)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, May, 1972 (Box-folder 127/1)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, June-August, 1972 (Box-folder 127/2)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, September, 1972 (Box-folder 127/3)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, October-November, 1972 (Box-folder 127/4)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, November-December, 1972 (Box-folder 127/5)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, January-February, 1973 (Box-folder 127/6)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, March-April, 1973 (Box-folder 127/7)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, August-September, 1973 (Box-folder 127/8)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, November-April, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 127/9)
        - Report to Club Treasurer, May-July, 1974 (Box-folder 127/10)
        - Request to Forward letters to Trophy Owners, 1988 (Box-folder 127/11)
        - Requests for Instructions, Charts, and Publications, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 127/12-13)
        - Requests for Permission to Publish, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 127/14)
        - Requests for Remeasurement, 1992 (Box-folder 127/15)
        - Requests for Reproduction of Materials, 1968 (Box-folder 127/16)
        - Resolution of Measurement Problems, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 127/17)
        - Resolution of Scoring Problems, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 128/1)
        - Richard King Foundation Grant, Correspondence, 1952-1970 (Box-folder 128/2)
        - Rocky Mountain Goat, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 128/3)
        - Roland Ward's Records of Big Game, Correspondence, 1933-1970 (Box-folder 128/4)
        - Committee Roster, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 128/5)
        - Dr. Elmer Rusten, Correspondence, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 128/6)
        - Safari Club International, Awards Program, Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 128/7)
        - Scoring Questions and Decisions, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 128/8)
        - Scoring System, Correspondence, 1950 (Box-folder 128/9-10)
        - Scoring System Revision, Correspondence, 1940-1964 (Box-folder 128/11-12)
        - Scrapbook, 1952-1953 (Box-folder OS 224/4)
        - Sheep, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 128/13)
        - Smithsonian Institution, 1931-1973 (Box-folder 129/1)
        - Snyder Elk Dispute, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 129/2)
        - Species Classification Questions, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 129/3)
        - Specific Trophy Problems, 1957 (Box-folder 129/4)
        - Statistics, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 129/5)
        - Strategic Issues and Options Input, 1999 (Box-folder 129/6)
        - Subcommittee on Big Game Classification, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 129/7)
        - Subcommittee on Boundaries and Classification, Memoranda and Report, 1975 (Box-folder 129/8)
        - Subcommittee on Competition Judging and Procedure, 1947-1965 (Box-folder 129/9)
        - Suggestions to Official Measurers, 1974 (Box-folder 129/10)
        - Territorial Limits of North American Big Game, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 129/11)
        - Emily Toerge, Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 129/12)
        - Trophies Taken Within Fenced Enclosures, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 129/13)
        - Trophy Shipping Instructions, 1968 (Box-folder 129/14)
        - Trophy Submission Indictments, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 129/15)
        - Vancouver Sun, Correspondence, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 129/16)
        - Wapiti (Elk), 1934-1969 (Box-folder 129/17)
        - Robert S. Waters, Chairman, Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 129/18)
        - Wilderness World Limited, Record Big Game, Limited Edition Prints, 1974 (Box-folder 129/19)
        - Wolves, 1968 (Box-folder 129/20)
        - Wrangell Sheep, Correspondence, 1960 (Box-folder 129/21)
        - Philip Wright, Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box-folder 130/1-2)
      - Committee - Friends of North American Big Game, 1947- 1964; Sub-sub-subseries 2; 0.5 linear feet
        Sub-sub-subseries 2 includes materials created by the Friends of North American Big Game Committee, a group that financially supported the North American Big Game Committee through subscriptions from the early 1950s through the early 1960s. Materials include correspondence, big game census figures and subscription information.
        - Friends of North American Big Game Committee, Big Game Census Figures, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 130/3)
        - Friends of North American Big Game Committee, Correspondence, 1952-1964 (Box-folder 130/4)
        - Friends of North American Big Game Committee, Subscriber Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 130/5)
        - Friends of North American Big Game Committee, Subscriptions, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 130/6-8)
      - Committees - Other, 1949-1974; Sub-sub-subseries 3; 0.25 linear feet